<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kaikeru</title>
    <link>https://blog.kaikeru.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on kaikeru</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 14:50:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.kaikeru.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JLPT</title>
      <link>https://blog.kaikeru.com/post/20190208-jlpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 14:50:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kaikeru.com/post/20190208-jlpt/</guid>
      <description>This is hard for me to admit, but I&amp;rsquo;ve failed at hitting the same goal every year for the last 10 years. I want to pass the Japanese Language Proficiency Test (JLPT). The test is broken into levels N5 -&amp;gt; N1. Each level tests your reading and listening skills. N5 is basic Japanese where N1 is hard enough to make fluent speakers second guess their education.
The test is a bureaucratic take on Japanese language and your mastery over it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Website Hosting with Github and DevOps</title>
      <link>https://blog.kaikeru.com/post/20181228-freestaticsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kaikeru.com/post/20181228-freestaticsite/</guid>
      <description>Paying for website hosting is passé. You can easily host with Wordpress, Tumblr, or many other solutions. The downside to these free hosted services (applications, really) is free means you&amp;rsquo;re the product one way or another. Maybe they put adds on your blog, maybe they sell your data. Also, what happens if that company goes under? Where does your corner of the internet go?
I&amp;rsquo;m a proponent of not relying on other services to build my content if I can help it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nihongo Tools</title>
      <link>https://blog.kaikeru.com/project/nihongo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 13:26:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kaikeru.com/project/nihongo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://blog.kaikeru.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kaikeru.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>Kyle Wagner Senior level software engineer with a specialty in DevOps.
Work Experience Senior Software Engineer - Devops/Automation - Xpansiv November 2018 to Present
 Lead automation engineer for deployment and QA pipelines. Specialist and evangelist for testing automation. Expert in Terraform and AWS Elastic Container Services  Director of Quality Engineering / Lead DevOps Engineer - RiskSense, Inc January 2018 to October 2018
 Managed the QA team and automation team and acted as release coordinator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>